<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Jeffjdaniels</title>
    <link href="http://jeffjdaniels.tk/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="http://jeffjdaniels.tk" />
    <updated>2018-10-18T18:17:47+07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>daniels</name>
    </author>
    <id>http://jeffjdaniels.tk</id>

    <entry>
        <title>My Name is Jeff J Daniels</title>
        <author>
            <name>daniels</name>
        </author>
        <link href="http://jeffjdaniels.tk/my-name-is-jeff-j-daniels.html"/>
        <id>http://jeffjdaniels.tk/my-name-is-jeff-j-daniels.html</id>

        <updated>2018-10-14T07:12:35+07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="http://jeffjdaniels.tk/media/posts/2/" alt="" />
                    My approach to cinema has always been good for more technical projects. I shot, monitored and designed visual effects for many productions involving practical and visual effects using chroma-keying, motion control, Match-move/tracing, miniature photography, and 360-degree VR. These productions present unique challenges, but offer a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="http://jeffjdaniels.tk/media/posts/2/" alt="" />
                <p>My approach to cinema has always been good for more technical projects. I shot, monitored and designed visual effects for many productions involving practical and visual effects using chroma-keying, motion control, Match-move/tracing, miniature photography, and 360-degree VR.</p>
<p><img src="http://jeffjdaniels.tk/media/posts/2/Capture.JPG" alt="" width="460" height="290"><br><br>These productions present unique challenges, but offer a very rewarding experience. It's exciting to be always learning and looking for new ways to achieve challenges. The key to the removal of visual effects is to adequately plan pre-production, define supervision and creativity in post-production. <br><br>I was impressed by having a creative evolutionary vision, a technical basis, and a passion to tell stories with each project that I am gifted to be part of; Large or small, commercial or narrative. <br><br>My work and desire for new experiences took me from coast to coast and around the world. The journey expands the human perspective and stimulates creativity, so I appreciate a career that gives me the opportunity to do so. my favorite food is <a href="https://lafriedchickenfest.com">fried chicken</a><br><br>Born and bred in southeastern Wisconsin, I have a title of Webster-St. Louis University in film production, and I'm based in Los Angeles, CA.</p>
<p>website: <a href="http://calico-kids.com">calico-kids.com</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
